<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">SaudeEmCasa</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="km">km</string>
    <string name="meters">m</string>

    <string name="program_drug">Popular Pharmacy</string>
    <string name="program_hospital">Better in Home</string>
    <string name="title_activity_hospital_maps">Map</string>

    <string name="hospital_address">Address:</string>
    <string name="hospital_telephone">Phone:</string>
    <string name="hospital_evaluation">Evaluation:</string>
    <string name="hospital_save">Save</string>

    <string name="drugstore_CEP">Postal Code:</string>
    <string name="drugstore_name">drugstoreName</string>
    <string name="drugstore_address">Address:</string>
    <string name="drugstore_telephone">Phone:</string>
    <string name="drugstore_evaluation">Evaluation:</string>
    <string name="drugstore_save">Save</string>

    <string name="infoScreenDrugstore">The Brazil Popular Pharmacy Program has to be an initiative of
        the Federal Government authorizing the Oswaldo Cruz Foundation (FIOCRUZ) to provide medicines
        by compensation, and by Decree No. 5,090, of May 20, 2004, which regulates Law 10,858 and
        establishes the Popular Pharmacy program Brazil. The units themselves have a list of 112 items,
        including drugs and male condoms, which are dispensed by its cost, a reduction of up to 90% of
        market value. The condition for the purchase of medicines available in the units, in this case,
        is the presentation document with photo, in stating your Social Security number, along with a
        medical or dental prescription.
         Importantly, only the Own Network accepts prescriptions written by dentists.</string>

    <string name="infoScreenMelhorEmCasa">Best Home program is related to health program created by
        the Federal Government in 2013, with the following proposals:
        Service people in need of motor rehabilitation, elderly, chronic patients without worsening
        or post-surgical situation. Improve and expand the SUS assistance to patients with health
        complaints that can receive care at home, and close to family.
        Contribute to the recovery of disease, since care and family care coupled with adequate
        health care become important elements for the patient's recovery.</string>

    <string name="infoScreenSaudeEmCasa">The application Home Health, aims to facilitate the user's
        Best Home program, ways to find Hospitals, Clinics or closest to the patient establishments,
        taking into account the issue of difficulty of displacement thereof. In addition, the
        application also provides the locations of drugstores in Brazil, so that users can locate and
        gain access to potential drug treatments your health.\n";</string>

</resources>
